toolwale.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy - Toolwale.com

****The User hereby consents, expresses and agrees that he has read and fully understands the Privacy Policy of ToolWale.com the Website. The user further consents that the terms and contents of such Privacy Policy are acceptable to him.****

  1. ToolWale.com is concerned about the privacy of its users accessing its website located at www.ToolWale.com and has provided this Privacy Policy to familiarise You with the manner in which ToolWale.com collects, uses and discloses information collected through the Website.
  2. This Privacy Policy explains how ToolWale.com collects personal as well non-personal information, categorized as mandatory or voluntary uses, discloses and protects such information through the Website. In Personal Information data that can be used to uniquely identify or to contact a single person. Personal Information for the purposes of the Policy includes but not limited to the information regarding consumer’s name, address, telephone number, date of birth, gender and e-mail address.
  3. You may need to provide ToolWale.com your Personal Information during the course of using some services of the ToolWale.com. For example while creating a User ID, provide information in Your account while registering on the Website or provide financial information while making an online purchase, upload content, participate in any online survey or contest and communicate with ToolWale’s customer service by phone, email or provide reviews for the content available on the Website.
  4. ToolWale.com endeavour to ensure the security, privacy and integrity of your Personal Information and to protect Personal Information against unauthorized access or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction on the web.
